# KENNY LAI

Full Stack Web Developer

# **CONTACT DETAILS:**

Phone: 0421128808

Email: kenny791@gmail.com

Linkedin: kenwebdev

Website: kenwebdev.netlify.app

Github: kenny791

Location: Melbourne, Australia

# **EDUCATION**

2023 Coder Academy

Diploma of Information Technology

2015 RMIT University

Bachelor of Engineering - Electrical

## **SKILLS**

- HTML & CSS
- Javascript
- Python
- PostgreSQL
- Flask
- MongoDB
- Express.js
- React.js
- Node.js
- Git

## **PROFILE**

Current coding bootcamp student at Coder Academy, studying fullstack web development. Technologies learnt include, Javascript, Python, HTML & CSS, PostgreSQL, Flask and MERN.

Bringing 6 years of consulting experience from the construction industry, time management, cross team collaboration, and quality of work are key priorities.

## **EXPERIENCE**

### SEASONAL MAIL OFFICER

Australia Post, Nov 2022 - Dec 2022

- Receiving and processing of incoming mail: Letter and parcels from Melbourne that are required to be sent interstate are sorted and forwarded to the appropriate air or land transport.
- Operating material handling equipment: This includes pallet jacks, conveyor belts, and other equipment to move items are the facility
- Ensuring safety and cleanliness: This involves following safety protocols and keeping the facility clean and organised.

#### **ELECTRICAL ENGINEER**

#### TJ Consulting Engineers, Jan 2022 - Jul 2022

- Design and documentation of electrical services: Produced services drawings for electrical trades in accordance with all relevant Australian Standards and National Construction Code.
- Lighting calculations: Using lighting models to produce room lighting simulations for the calculation of the appropriate lighting levels.
- Project management: Liaised with interior designers & architects during the design stage, and electrical trades during to construction to ensuring the timely completion of projects.
- Authority applications: Liaised with the electricity network distributors and communication services provide.
- Site inspections: Undertook preliminary investigation of sites, during the startup of projects to highlight any potential issues, and during practical completion of the project to confirm compliance of installation of electrical services in accordance with electrical services drawings.
- Collaborated with cross-functional teams: Facilitated and communicated needs of other engineering disciplines for a coordinated project.

#### **ELECTRICAL ENGINEER**

#### Compass Engineering Group, Apr 2018 - Dec 2021

- Design and documentation of electrical services: Produced services drawings for electrical trades in accordance with all relevant Australian Standards and National Construction Code.
- Trained junior staff: Provide training for documentation software such as Revit and Autocad, in addition to office procedures.
- Document transmission: Collated files from all teams to be sent to external stakeholders and ensured document register was up to date.
- Set-up of services documentation files:
- Project management: Liaised with interior designers & architects during the design stage, and electrical trades during to construction to ensuring the timely completion of projects.
- Lighting calculations: Using lighting models to produce room lighting simulations for the calculation of the appropriate lighting levels.
- Authority applications: Liaised with the electricity network distributors and communication services provide.
- Site inspections: Undertook preliminary investigation of sites, during the startup of projects to highlight
  any potential issues, and during practical completion of the project to confirm compliance of
  installation of electrical services in accordance with electrical services drawings.
- Collaborated with cross-functional teams: Facilitated and communicated needs of other engineering disciplines for a coordinated project.

#### **ELECTRICAL ENGINEER**

#### ECM Group, Aug 2016 - Apr 2018

- Preliminary design and documentation of electrical services: Produced high level electrical services
  designs and assissted seniro engineers with calculations and modelling.
- Document transmission: Collated files from all teams to be sent to external stakeholders and ensured document register was up to date.
- Set-up of services documentation files:
- Lighting calculations: Using lighting models to produce room lighting simulations for the calculation of the appropriate lighting levels.
- Collaborated with cross-functional teams: Facilitated and communicated needs of other engineering disciplines for a coordinated project.

# **REFERENCES**

Available upon request.